const level14questions = [
    {
        "question": "66 + 40 = ?",
        "options": ["158", "28", "106", "180"],
        "answer": "106"
      },
      {
        "question": "35 + 95 = ?",
        "options": ["130", "140", "146", "106"],
        "answer": "130"
      },
      {
        "question": "11 + 77 = ?",
        "options": ["190", "162", "88", "132"],
        "answer": "88"
      },
      {
        "question": "82 + 57 = ?",
        "options": ["138", "139", "144", "34"],
        "answer": "139"
      },
      {
        "question": "83 + 59 = ?",
        "options": ["142", "70", "170", "114"],
        "answer": "142"
      },
      {
        "question": "55 + 38 = ?",
        "options": ["156", "93", "172", "82"],
        "answer": "93"
      },
      {
        "question": "97 + 68 = ?",
        "options": ["82", "165", "78", "108"],
        "answer": "165"
      },
      {
        "question": "71 + 87 = ?",
        "options": ["158", "98", "60", "134"],
        "answer": "158"
      },
      {
        "question": "34 + 79 = ?",
        "options": ["113", "198", "192", "132"],
        "answer": "113"
      },
      {
        "question": "34 + 78 = ?",
        "options": ["72", "34", "76", "112"],
        "answer": "112"
      },
      {
        "question": "62 + 90 = ?",
        "options": ["152", "62", "66", "30"],
        "answer": "152"
      },
      {
        "question": "15 + 72 = ?",
        "options": ["124", "74", "87", "144"],
        "answer": "87"
      },
      {
        "question": "27 + 14 = ?",
        "options": ["30", "41", "36", "64"],
        "answer": "41"
      },
      {
        "question": "99 + 82 = ?",
        "options": ["90", "181", "86", "64"],
        "answer": "181"
      },
      {
        "question": "93 + 17 = ?",
        "options": ["136", "180", "110", "100"],
        "answer": "110"
      },
      {
        "question": "89 + 71 = ?",
        "options": ["160", "144", "114", "106"],
        "answer": "160"
      },
      {
        "question": "61 + 81 = ?",
        "options": ["164", "142", "68", "30"],
        "answer": "142"
      },
      {
        "question": "67 + 83 = ?",
        "options": ["190", "150", "20", "50"],
        "answer": "150"
      },
      {
        "question": "84 + 34 = ?",
        "options": ["118", "42", "196", "182"],
        "answer": "118"
      },
      {
        "question": "42 + 73 = ?",
        "options": ["92", "192", "115", "120"],
        "answer": "115"
      },
      {
        "question": "83 + 95 = ?",
        "options": ["118", "178", "96", "158"],
        "answer": "178"
      },
      {
        "question": "64 + 28 = ?",
        "options": ["66", "26", "62", "92"],
        "answer": "92"
      },
      {
        "question": "84 + 48 = ?",
        "options": ["84", "132", "60", "54"],
        "answer": "132"
      },
      {
        "question": "64 + 35 = ?",
        "options": ["158", "99", "168", "44"],
        "answer": "99"
      },
      {
        "question": "26 + 22 = ?",
        "options": ["178", "172", "108", "48"],
        "answer": "48"
      },
    
    {
        "question": "34 + 50 = ?",
        "options": ["84", "136", "72", "162"],
        "answer": "84"
      },
      {
        "question": "14 + 33 = ?",
        "options": ["186", "162", "92", "47"],
        "answer": "47"
      },
      {
        "question": "91 + 56 = ?",
        "options": ["70", "96", "34", "147"],
        "answer": "147"
      },
      {
        "question": "82 + 25 = ?",
        "options": ["74", "107", "34", "188"],
        "answer": "107"
      },
      {
        "question": "55 + 27 = ?",
        "options": ["112", "188", "82", "92"],
        "answer": "82"
      },
      {
        "question": "37 + 60 = ?",
        "options": ["182", "97", "196", "42"],
        "answer": "97"
      },
      {
        "question": "82 + 50 = ?",
        "options": ["188", "134", "132", "92"],
        "answer": "132"
      },
      {
        "question": "15 + 66 = ?",
        "options": ["81", "128", "52", "64"],
        "answer": "81"
      },
      {
        "question": "83 + 58 = ?",
        "options": ["102", "141", "128", "78"],
        "answer": "141"
      },
      {
        "question": "18 + 44 = ?",
        "options": ["120", "156", "62", "134"],
        "answer": "62"
      },
      {
        "question": "79 + 43 = ?",
        "options": ["122", "92", "182", "72"],
        "answer": "122"
      },
      {
        "question": "19 + 80 = ?",
        "options": ["80", "40", "176", "99"],
        "answer": "99"
      },
      {
        "question": "49 + 78 = ?",
        "options": ["98", "72", "127", "28"],
        "answer": "127"
      },
      {
        "question": "83 + 11 = ?",
        "options": ["46", "154", "94", "32"],
        "answer": "94"
      },
      {
        "question": "36 + 99 = ?",
        "options": ["108", "146", "135", "162"],
        "answer": "135"
      },
      {
        "question": "11 + 64 = ?",
        "options": ["184", "134", "75", "34"],
        "answer": "75"
      },
      {
        "question": "78 + 71 = ?",
        "options": ["154", "196", "80", "149"],
        "answer": "149"
      },
      {
        "question": "91 + 11 = ?",
        "options": ["72", "170", "102", "54"],
        "answer": "102"
      },
      {
        "question": "24 + 45 = ?",
        "options": ["44", "69", "134", "24"],
        "answer": "69"
      },
      {
        "question": "53 + 35 = ?",
        "options": ["88", "190", "120", "104"],
        "answer": "88"
      },
      {
        "question": "49 + 95 = ?",
        "options": ["170", "144", "72", "24"],
        "answer": "144"
      },
      {
        "question": "20 + 86 = ?",
        "options": ["26", "82", "106", "144"],
        "answer": "106"
      },
      {
        "question": "64 + 32 = ?",
        "options": ["96", "152", "78", "68"],
        "answer": "96"
      },
      {
        "question": "16 + 65 = ?",
        "options": ["48", "81", "86", "90"],
        "answer": "81"
      },
      {
        "question": "73 + 82 = ?",
        "options": ["166", "140", "42", "155"],
        "answer": "155"
      },
    {
        "question": "66 + 21 = ?",
        "options": ["87", "182", "72", "54"],
        "answer": "87"
      },
      {
        "question": "27 + 49 = ?",
        "options": ["44", "112", "28", "76"],
        "answer": "76"
      },
      {
        "question": "81 + 11 = ?",
        "options": ["92", "176", "100", "156"],
        "answer": "92"
      },
      {
        "question": "60 + 48 = ?",
        "options": ["94", "118", "160", "108"],
        "answer": "108"
      },
      {
        "question": "82 + 62 = ?",
        "options": ["144", "186", "188", "168"],
        "answer": "144"
      },
      {
        "question": "56 + 35 = ?",
        "options": ["104", "91", "100", "132"],
        "answer": "91"
      },
      {
        "question": "25 + 58 = ?",
        "options": ["94", "83", "144", "54"],
        "answer": "83"
      },
      {
        "question": "51 + 35 = ?",
        "options": ["192", "86", "148", "118"],
        "answer": "86"
      },
      {
        "question": "19 + 23 = ?",
        "options": ["62", "186", "42", "78"],
        "answer": "42"
      },
      {
        "question": "39 + 47 = ?",
        "options": ["182", "92", "86", "114"],
        "answer": "86"
      },
      {
        "question": "36 + 20 = ?",
        "options": ["54", "56", "38", "82"],
        "answer": "56"
      },
      {
        "question": "26 + 62 = ?",
        "options": ["66", "80", "90", "88"],
        "answer": "88"
      },
      {
        "question": "37 + 24 = ?",
        "options": ["146", "28", "176", "61"],
        "answer": "61"
      },
      {
        "question": "60 + 76 = ?",
        "options": ["178", "136", "196", "116"],
        "answer": "136"
      },
      {
        "question": "56 + 39 = ?",
        "options": ["146", "152", "95", "54"],
        "answer": "95"
      },
      {
        "question": "15 + 60 = ?",
        "options": ["144", "75", "148", "28"],
        "answer": "75"
      },
      {
        "question": "40 + 51 = ?",
        "options": ["190", "91", "30", "162"],
        "answer": "91"
      },
      {
        "question": "41 + 29 = ?",
        "options": ["70", "60", "142", "140"],
        "answer": "70"
      },
      {
        "question": "31 + 34 = ?",
        "options": ["38", "90", "172", "65"],
        "answer": "65"
      },
      {
        "question": "55 + 90 = ?",
        "options": ["198", "68", "145", "174"],
        "answer": "145"
      },
      {
        "question": "25 + 28 = ?",
        "options": ["53", "182", "162", "66"],
        "answer": "53"
      },
      {
        "question": "89 + 83 = ?",
        "options": ["50", "100", "38", "172"],
        "answer": "172"
      },
      {
        "question": "29 + 79 = ?",
        "options": ["108", "68", "166", "158"],
        "answer": "108"
      },
      {
        "question": "63 + 21 = ?",
        "options": ["32", "84", "172", "182"],
        "answer": "84"
      },
      {
        "question": "20 + 25 = ?",
        "options": ["114", "45", "168", "138"],
        "answer": "45"
      },
    
    {
        "question": "95 + 45 = ?",
        "options": ["102", "64", "30", "140"],
        "answer": "140"
      },
      {
        "question": "43 + 21 = ?",
        "options": ["100", "170", "64", "188"],
        "answer": "64"
      },
      {
        "question": "14 + 50 = ?",
        "options": ["198", "64", "78", "62"],
        "answer": "64"
      },
      {
        "question": "76 + 78 = ?",
        "options": ["82", "44", "154", "32"],
        "answer": "154"
      },
      {
        "question": "88 + 52 = ?",
        "options": ["58", "52", "70", "140"],
        "answer": "140"
      },
      {
        "question": "16 + 64 = ?",
        "options": ["26", "64", "66", "80"],
        "answer": "80"
      },
      {
        "question": "63 + 81 = ?",
        "options": ["64", "26", "92", "144"],
        "answer": "144"
      },
      {
        "question": "13 + 92 = ?",
        "options": ["98", "105", "196", "32"],
        "answer": "105"
      },
      {
        "question": "54 + 94 = ?",
        "options": ["148", "166", "48", "198"],
        "answer": "148"
      },
      {
        "question": "91 + 92 = ?",
        "options": ["178", "166", "183", "44"],
        "answer": "183"
      },
      {
        "question": "60 + 31 = ?",
        "options": ["158", "91", "60", "168"],
        "answer": "91"
      },
      {
        "question": "58 + 73 = ?",
        "options": ["131", "48", "64", "80"],
        "answer": "131"
      },
      {
        "question": "44 + 35 = ?",
        "options": ["138", "124", "120", "79"],
        "answer": "79"
      },
      {
        "question": "88 + 89 = ?",
        "options": ["28", "177", "74", "116"],
        "answer": "177"
      },
      {
        "question": "70 + 73 = ?",
        "options": ["90", "143", "118", "190"],
        "answer": "143"
      },
      {
        "question": "90 + 55 = ?",
        "options": ["70", "164", "145", "22"],
        "answer": "145"
      },
      {
        "question": "30 + 22 = ?",
        "options": ["52", "88", "148", "20"],
        "answer": "52"
      },
      {
        "question": "55 + 91 = ?",
        "options": ["96", "146", "166", "20"],
        "answer": "146"
      },
      {
        "question": "21 + 41 = ?",
        "options": ["98", "94", "62", "182"],
        "answer": "62"
      },
      {
        "question": "76 + 38 = ?",
        "options": ["20", "106", "132", "114"],
        "answer": "114"
      },
      {
        "question": "51 + 96 = ?",
        "options": ["60", "122", "160", "147"],
        "answer": "147"
      },
      {
        "question": "45 + 34 = ?",
        "options": ["64", "26", "79", "180"],
        "answer": "79"
      },
      {
        "question": "30 + 68 = ?",
        "options": ["84", "98", "114", "122"],
        "answer": "98"
      },
      {
        "question": "26 + 75 = ?",
        "options": ["101", "50", "26", "184"],
        "answer": "101"
      },
      {
        "question": "73 + 52 = ?",
        "options": ["192", "125", "28", "104"],
        "answer": "125"
      },
    {
        "question": "762 + 450 = ?",
        "options": ["1846", "1244", "1212", "692"],
        "answer": "1212"
      },
      {
        "question": "274 + 575 = ?",
        "options": ["849", "1986", "654", "730"],
        "answer": "849"
      },
      {
        "question": "537 + 511 = ?",
        "options": ["1048", "464", "296", "1316"],
        "answer": "1048"
      },
      {
        "question": "189 + 488 = ?",
        "options": ["960", "1150", "677", "1748"],
        "answer": "677"
      },
      {
        "question": "925 + 136 = ?",
        "options": ["1484", "1061", "374", "858"],
        "answer": "1061"
      },
      {
        "question": "945 + 631 = ?",
        "options": ["1576", "1538", "778", "820"],
        "answer": "1576"
      },
      {
        "question": "511 + 338 = ?",
        "options": ["510", "1028", "849", "1114"],
        "answer": "849"
      },
      {
        "question": "230 + 345 = ?",
        "options": ["575", "1758", "502", "852"],
        "answer": "575"
      },
      {
        "question": "833 + 986 = ?",
        "options": ["450", "1819", "280", "1890"],
        "answer": "1819"
      },
      {
        "question": "601 + 199 = ?",
        "options": ["732", "1112", "800", "474"],
        "answer": "800"
      },
      {
        "question": "568 + 502 = ?",
        "options": ["262", "510", "660", "1070"],
        "answer": "1070"
      },
      {
        "question": "862 + 663 = ?",
        "options": ["1724", "1525", "204", "408"],
        "answer": "1525"
      },
      {
        "question": "534 + 458 = ?",
        "options": ["1192", "992", "266", "852"],
        "answer": "992"
      },
      {
        "question": "499 + 718 = ?",
        "options": ["1366", "812", "928", "1217"],
        "answer": "1217"
      },
      {
        "question": "367 + 534 = ?",
        "options": ["816", "1852", "208", "901"],
        "answer": "901"
      },
      {
        "question": "768 + 717 = ?",
        "options": ["1206", "1485", "1534", "840"],
        "answer": "1485"
      },
      {
        "question": "842 + 178 = ?",
        "options": ["1786", "1020", "780", "1278"],
        "answer": "1020"
      },
      {
        "question": "955 + 792 = ?",
        "options": ["1242", "600", "474", "1747"],
        "answer": "1747"
      },
      {
        "question": "247 + 900 = ?",
        "options": ["1147", "396", "562", "852"],
        "answer": "1147"
      },
      {
        "question": "819 + 346 = ?",
        "options": ["338", "1165", "1162", "1444"],
        "answer": "1165"
      },
      {
        "question": "744 + 620 = ?",
        "options": ["1236", "1364", "1696", "640"],
        "answer": "1364"
      },
      {
        "question": "504 + 795 = ?",
        "options": ["1299", "724", "580", "1342"],
        "answer": "1299"
      },
      {
        "question": "277 + 468 = ?",
        "options": ["1182", "342", "745", "382"],
        "answer": "745"
      },
      {
        "question": "257 + 665 = ?",
        "options": ["1808", "700", "922", "1606"],
        "answer": "922"
      },
      {
        "question": "971 + 611 = ?",
        "options": ["1582", "1668", "298", "1412"],
        "answer": "1582"
      },
    {
        "question": "285 + 444 = ?",
        "options": ["1870", "1728", "729", "564"],
        "answer": "729"
      },
      {
        "question": "561 + 380 = ?",
        "options": ["444", "941", "1096", "1160"],
        "answer": "941"
      },
      {
        "question": "251 + 958 = ?",
        "options": ["1188", "1209", "598", "726"],
        "answer": "1209"
      },
      {
        "question": "405 + 404 = ?",
        "options": ["809", "1240", "644", "738"],
        "answer": "809"
      },
      {
        "question": "277 + 517 = ?",
        "options": ["1260", "1540", "690", "794"],
        "answer": "794"
      },
      {
        "question": "332 + 399 = ?",
        "options": ["1592", "1712", "1326", "731"],
        "answer": "731"
      },
      {
        "question": "109 + 904 = ?",
        "options": ["1013", "1318", "564", "1646"],
        "answer": "1013"
      },
      {
        "question": "248 + 827 = ?",
        "options": ["1074", "350", "1075", "488"],
        "answer": "1075"
      },
      {
        "question": "506 + 388 = ?",
        "options": ["894", "876", "922", "1160"],
        "answer": "894"
      },
      {
        "question": "724 + 813 = ?",
        "options": ["1834", "1537", "944", "1950"],
        "answer": "1537"
      },
      {
        "question": "915 + 560 = ?",
        "options": ["1616", "1926", "1475", "538"],
        "answer": "1475"
      },
      {
        "question": "469 + 211 = ?",
        "options": ["208", "1366", "448", "680"],
        "answer": "680"
      },
      {
        "question": "157 + 861 = ?",
        "options": ["392", "1118", "1018", "1792"],
        "answer": "1018"
      },
      {
        "question": "110 + 518 = ?",
        "options": ["1216", "1982", "628", "1098"],
        "answer": "628"
      },
      {
        "question": "843 + 693 = ?",
        "options": ["286", "1548", "1114", "1536"],
        "answer": "1536"
      },
      {
        "question": "876 + 503 = ?",
        "options": ["1122", "462", "1379", "1186"],
        "answer": "1379"
      },
      {
        "question": "256 + 224 = ?",
        "options": ["486", "1408", "480", "1028"],
        "answer": "480"
      },
      {
        "question": "105 + 802 = ?",
        "options": ["1146", "1654", "1768", "907"],
        "answer": "907"
      },
      {
        "question": "530 + 285 = ?",
        "options": ["576", "1356", "774", "815"],
        "answer": "815"
      },
      {
        "question": "598 + 989 = ?",
        "options": ["302", "786", "454", "1587"],
        "answer": "1587"
      },
      {
        "question": "383 + 552 = ?",
        "options": ["1682", "935", "336", "1344"],
        "answer": "935"
      },
      {
        "question": "583 + 163 = ?",
        "options": ["1368", "1544", "1960", "746"],
        "answer": "746"
      },
      {
        "question": "536 + 772 = ?",
        "options": ["1508", "446", "1308", "1636"],
        "answer": "1308"
      },
      {
        "question": "545 + 492 = ?",
        "options": ["1220", "464", "986", "1037"],
        "answer": "1037"
      },
      {
        "question": "352 + 510 = ?",
        "options": ["862", "1896", "310", "986"],
        "answer": "862"
      },
    
    {
        "question": "106 + 964 = ?",
        "options": ["1070", "1338", "202", "1898"],
        "answer": "1070"
      },
      {
        "question": "865 + 304 = ?",
        "options": ["960", "414", "1086", "1169"],
        "answer": "1169"
      },
      {
        "question": "568 + 820 = ?",
        "options": ["1508", "208", "670", "1388"],
        "answer": "1388"
      },
      {
        "question": "489 + 287 = ?",
        "options": ["1132", "384", "776", "928"],
        "answer": "776"
      },
      {
        "question": "140 + 401 = ?",
        "options": ["626", "1528", "874", "541"],
        "answer": "541"
      },
      {
        "question": "572 + 759 = ?",
        "options": ["1624", "818", "1331", "468"],
        "answer": "1331"
      },
      {
        "question": "734 + 761 = ?",
        "options": ["1012", "1495", "566", "1744"],
        "answer": "1495"
      },
      {
        "question": "387 + 224 = ?",
        "options": ["611", "1792", "262", "732"],
        "answer": "611"
      },
      {
        "question": "372 + 484 = ?",
        "options": ["1050", "1210", "500", "856"],
        "answer": "856"
      },
      {
        "question": "544 + 818 = ?",
        "options": ["760", "1362", "1918", "656"],
        "answer": "1362"
      },
      {
        "question": "877 + 582 = ?",
        "options": ["1459", "1436", "944", "1820"],
        "answer": "1459"
      },
      {
        "question": "159 + 807 = ?",
        "options": ["1792", "1306", "1242", "966"],
        "answer": "966"
      },
      {
        "question": "199 + 778 = ?",
        "options": ["977", "910", "1274", "1632"],
        "answer": "977"
      },
      {
        "question": "615 + 157 = ?",
        "options": ["772", "1018", "1338", "1268"],
        "answer": "772"
      },
      {
        "question": "848 + 245 = ?",
        "options": ["1093", "558", "1572", "502"],
        "answer": "1093"
      },
      {
        "question": "867 + 110 = ?",
        "options": ["964", "1544", "977", "712"],
        "answer": "977"
      },
      {
        "question": "502 + 263 = ?",
        "options": ["1464", "1760", "1482", "765"],
        "answer": "765"
      },
      {
        "question": "468 + 673 = ?",
        "options": ["1230", "622", "752", "1141"],
        "answer": "1141"
      },
      {
        "question": "633 + 177 = ?",
        "options": ["506", "798", "866", "810"],
        "answer": "810"
      },
      {
        "question": "872 + 336 = ?",
        "options": ["1208", "1798", "1722", "1782"],
        "answer": "1208"
      },
      {
        "question": "464 + 873 = ?",
        "options": ["1337", "352", "416", "1964"],
        "answer": "1337"
      },
      {
        "question": "222 + 817 = ?",
        "options": ["720", "1039", "488", "252"],
        "answer": "1039"
      },
      {
        "question": "737 + 953 = ?",
        "options": ["1690", "1460", "776", "748"],
        "answer": "1690"
      },
      {
        "question": "419 + 810 = ?",
        "options": ["1350", "1498", "1678", "1229"],
        "answer": "1229"
      },
      {
        "question": "109 + 737 = ?",
        "options": ["846", "1610", "626", "1280"],
        "answer": "846"
      },
     {
        "question": "721 + 524 = ?",
        "options": ["1858", "590", "1544", "1245"],
        "answer": "1245"
      },
      {
        "question": "871 + 528 = ?",
        "options": ["1399", "386", "902", "1076"],
        "answer": "1399"
      },
      {
        "question": "354 + 960 = ?",
        "options": ["1456", "1300", "1314", "1840"],
        "answer": "1314"
      },
      {
        "question": "545 + 754 = ?",
        "options": ["300", "208", "1299", "926"],
        "answer": "1299"
      },
      {
        "question": "366 + 920 = ?",
        "options": ["1864", "1286", "542", "1330"],
        "answer": "1330"
      },
      {
        "question": "592 + 297 = ?",
        "options": ["889", "1770", "1486", "622"],
        "answer": "889"
      },
      {
        "question": "615 + 719 = ?",
        "options": ["1334", "226", "394", "402"],
        "answer": "1334"
      },
      {
        "question": "597 + 126 = ?",
        "options": ["1722", "570", "723", "1470"],
        "answer": "723"
      },
      {
        "question": "348 + 186 = ?",
        "options": ["1330", "1574", "534", "220"],
        "answer": "534"
      },
      {
        "question": "858 + 510 = ?",
        "options": ["296", "1672", "870", "1368"],
        "answer": "1368"
      },
      {
        "question": "906 + 472 = ?",
        "options": ["278", "1234", "1378", "1490"],
        "answer": "1378"
      },
      {
        "question": "551 + 345 = ?",
        "options": ["1776", "1552", "896", "1646"],
        "answer": "896"
      },
      {
        "question": "181 + 835 = ?",
        "options": ["706", "1016", "1322", "1188"],
        "answer": "1016"
      },
      {
        "question": "803 + 280 = ?",
        "options": ["1636", "280", "550", "1083"],
        "answer": "1083"
      },
      {
        "question": "276 + 852 = ?",
        "options": ["1180", "1162", "1128", "1294"],
        "answer": "1128"
      },
      {
        "question": "574 + 915 = ?",
        "options": ["288", "1896", "1340", "1489"],
        "answer": "1489"
      },
      {
        "question": "905 + 369 = ?",
        "options": ["1570", "1274", "1204", "274"],
        "answer": "1274"
      },
      {
        "question": "269 + 336 = ?",
        "options": ["1194", "605", "670", "1150"],
        "answer": "605"
      },
      {
        "question": "153 + 993 = ?",
        "options": ["974", "788", "1792", "1146"],
        "answer": "1146"
      },
      {
        "question": "729 + 948 = ?",
        "options": ["1677", "1360", "1528", "410"],
        "answer": "1677"
      },
      {
        "question": "644 + 689 = ?",
        "options": ["1333", "1308", "948", "1186"],
        "answer": "1333"
      },
      {
        "question": "448 + 115 = ?",
        "options": ["1630", "563", "476", "1296"],
        "answer": "563"
      },
      {
        "question": "609 + 218 = ?",
        "options": ["694", "548", "796", "827"],
        "answer": "827"
      },
      {
        "question": "233 + 710 = ?",
        "options": ["1656", "616", "1928", "943"],
        "answer": "943"
      },
      {
        "question": "936 + 577 = ?",
        "options": ["446", "1586", "1513", "972"],
        "answer": "1513"
      },
     {
        "question": "5596 + 8086 = ?",
        "options": ["19640", "13682", "3164", "3812"],
        "answer": "13682"
      },
      {
        "question": "5336 + 3654 = ?",
        "options": ["8990", "2266", "11416", "13988"],
        "answer": "8990"
      },
      {
        "question": "1653 + 1110 = ?",
        "options": ["14168", "2763", "3000", "13638"],
        "answer": "2763"
      },
      {
        "question": "7366 + 7337 = ?",
        "options": ["12380", "14134", "4444", "14703"],
        "answer": "14703"
      },
      {
        "question": "9723 + 5331 = ?",
        "options": ["15542", "15054", "9726", "17454"],
        "answer": "15054"
      },
      {
        "question": "1799 + 4104 = ?",
        "options": ["2340", "9102", "5903", "14082"],
        "answer": "5903"
      },
      {
        "question": "1580 + 7708 = ?",
        "options": ["9288", "2890", "5940", "9634"],
        "answer": "9288"
      },
      {
        "question": "3155 + 4386 = ?",
        "options": ["4666", "7210", "12172", "7541"],
        "answer": "7541"
      },
      {
        "question": "1629 + 9849 = ?",
        "options": ["19754", "5628", "11478", "3682"],
        "answer": "3682"
      },
      {
        "question": "7958 + 9919 = ?",
        "options": ["10996", "10690", "17877", "16732"],
        "answer": "17877"
      },
      {
        "question": "4600 + 2274 = ?",
        "options": ["12216", "6874", "10044", "19034"],
        "answer": "6874"
      },
      {
        "question": "9016 + 5431 = ?",
        "options": ["14447", "9590", "8974", "9052"],
        "answer": "14447"
      },
      {
        "question": "1304 + 4148 = ?",
        "options": ["5452", "17140", "6480", "7470"],
        "answer": "5452"
      },
      {
        "question": "3703 + 3691 = ?",
        "options": ["7394", "14594", "2248", "4618"],
        "answer": "7394"
      },
      {
        "question": "6981 + 3515 = ?",
        "options": ["15958", "10642", "6042", "10496"],
        "answer": "10496"
      },
      {
        "question": "6975 + 3962 = ?",
        "options": ["11016", "15814", "3578", "10937"],
        "answer": "10937"
      },
      {
        "question": "2111 + 3689 = ?",
        "options": ["10898", "5800", "8790", "3846"],
        "answer": "5800"
      },
      {
        "question": "3776 + 3693 = ?",
        "options": ["6404", "11696", "7469", "9146"],
        "answer": "7469"
      },
      {
        "question": "8645 + 9816 = ?",
        "options": ["18004", "18461", "7518", "17332"],
        "answer": "18461"
      },
      {
        "question": "5951 + 4601 = ?",
        "options": ["9564", "14882", "10552", "15930"],
        "answer": "10552"
      },
      {
        "question": "2364 + 1149 = ?",
        "options": ["13252", "16672", "10510", "3513"],
        "answer": "3513"
      },
      {
        "question": "2161 + 3674 = ?",
        "options": ["13644", "5378", "13220", "5835"],
        "answer": "5835"
      },
      {
        "question": "3426 + 5183 = ?",
        "options": ["19570", "13002", "6602", "8609"],
        "answer": "8609"
      },
      {
        "question": "2078 + 8137 = ?",
        "options": ["15142", "10215", "4178", "14612"],
        "answer": "10215"
      },
      {
        "question": "6044 + 5407 = ?",
        "options": ["11236", "11451", "13836", "15428"],
        "answer": "11451"
      },
        {
            question: "3920 + 8306 = ?",
            options: ["4974", "15998", "12226", "3430"],
            answer: "12226"
        },
        {
            question: "3913 + 7712 = ?",
            options: ["18514", "11625", "6026", "5716"],
            answer: "18514"
        },
        {
            question: "7223 + 2593 = ?",
            options: ["9816", "11724", "19990", "5222"],
            answer: "9816"
        },
        {
            question: "4253 + 6656 = ?",
            options: ["10909", "13228", "15242", "8988"],
            answer: "10909"
        },
        {
            question: "6741 + 6995 = ?",
            options: ["13736", "13550", "13718", "2018"],
            answer: "13736"
        },
        {
            question: "7022 + 6166 = ?",
            options: ["10274", "19988", "7706", "13188"],
            answer: "13188"
        },
        {
            question: "3564 + 3422 = ?",
            options: ["17404", "7324", "9676", "6986"],
            answer: "6986"
        },
        {
            question: "9610 + 4804 = ?",
            options: ["14414", "5876", "8902", "15726"],
            answer: "14414"
        },
        {
            question: "9535 + 1734 = ?",
            options: ["10402", "5118", "11590", "11269"],
            answer: "11269"
        },
        {
            question: "8073 + 6495 = ?",
            options: ["6044", "2916", "14568", "11804"],
            answer: "11804"
        },
        {
            question: "4833 + 1757 = ?",
            options: ["8902", "14484", "6590", "12830"],
            answer: "6590"
        },
        {
            question: "9363 + 5535 = ?",
            options: ["14898", "10480", "8002", "9878"],
            answer: "14898"
        },
        {
            question: "4343 + 7426 = ?",
            options: ["14374", "11769", "9396", "19756"],
            answer: "11769"
        },
        {
            question: "7585 + 4572 = ?",
            options: ["12157", "9018", "12266", "18016"],
            answer: "12157"
        },
        {
            question: "6335 + 3066 = ?",
            options: ["5478", "17534", "9401", "4060"],
            answer: "9401"
        },
        {
            question: "8862 + 6795 = ?",
            options: ["7314", "15657", "6920", "5114"],
            answer: "15657"
        },
        {
            question: "1970 + 4270 = ?",
            options: ["6240", "10626", "13438", "7812"],
            answer: "6240"
        },
        {
            question: "8780 + 2814 = ?",
            options: ["19528", "9236", "11594", "2488"],
            answer: "11594"
        },
        {
            question: "2821 + 2190 = ?",
            options: ["3990", "5011", "10510", "3406"],
            answer: "5011"
        },
        {
            question: "1825 + 8371 = ?",
            options: ["10196", "6058", "3894", "15104"],
            answer: "10196"
        },
        {
            question: "6333 + 1915 = ?",
            options: ["7320", "7788", "8248", "5708"],
            answer: "8248"
        },
        {
            question: "1010 + 6886 = ?",
            options: ["19024", "7896", "8288", "7470"],
            answer: "7896"
        },
        {
            question: "5564 + 2049 = ?",
            options: ["7613", "5532", "16544", "9324"],
            answer: "7613"
        },
        {
            question: "7108 + 5701 = ?",
            options: ["7938", "12809", "9564", "8812"],
            answer: "12809"
        },
        {
            question: "6405 + 9994 = ?",
            options: ["19004", "14424", "16166", "16399"],
            answer: "16399"
        },
    {
            question: "6943 + 7828 = ?",
            options: ["8504", "14771", "16058", "16908"],
            answer: "14771"
        },
        {
            question: "6608 + 1677 = ?",
            options: ["10676", "8285", "11892", "6746"],
            answer: "8285"
        },
        {
            question: "2475 + 1290 = ?",
            options: ["2992", "17084", "3765", "6568"],
            answer: "3765"
        },
        {
            question: "7523 + 9042 = ?",
            options: ["7748", "18820", "16565", "6400"],
            answer: "16565"
        },
        {
            question: "4533 + 6546 = ?",
            options: ["11079", "3758", "11238", "14022"],
            answer: "11079"
        },
        {
            question: "8521 + 5027 = ?",
            options: ["13548", "8032", "15694", "2668"],
            answer: "13548"
        },
        {
            question: "1995 + 4570 = ?",
            options: ["6565", "10956", "2818", "8176"],
            answer: "6565"
        },
        {
            question: "2820 + 9205 = ?",
            options: ["12025", "2890", "17690", "2570"],
            answer: "12025"
        },
        {
            question: "6636 + 9326 = ?",
            options: ["5552", "2016", "15962", "17408"],
            answer: "15962"
        },
        {
            question: "4792 + 4342 = ?",
            options: ["7920", "7954", "9134", "10806"],
            answer: "9134"
        },
        {
            question: "6208 + 6387 = ?",
            options: ["12595", "16698", "9792", "11968"],
            answer: "12595"
        },
        {
            question: "9498 + 4419 = ?",
            options: ["18772", "15520", "13917", "9006"],
            answer: "13917"
        },
        {
            question: "9479 + 3772 = ?",
            options: ["10744", "13251", "8120", "19702"],
            answer: "13251"
        },
        {
            question: "1974 + 4176 = ?",
            options: ["12810", "9822", "18744", "6150"],
            answer: "6150"
        },
        {
            question: "2852 + 6633 = ?",
            options: ["10834", "18008", "18362", "9485"],
            answer: "9485"
        },
        {
            question: "2944 + 9897 = ?",
            options: ["19032", "12182", "12841", "17550"],
            answer: "12841"
        },
        {
            question: "8627 + 4398 = ?",
            options: ["11114", "12634", "13025", "16140"],
            answer: "13025"
        },
        {
            question: "7773 + 4754 = ?",
            options: ["4674", "2666", "13496", "12527"],
            answer: "12527"
        },
        {
            question: "7553 + 6350 = ?",
            options: ["6678", "18230", "8704", "13903"],
            answer: "13903"
        },
        {
            question: "5588 + 6885 = ?",
            options: ["18432", "12473", "8094", "6076"],
            answer: "12473"
        },
        {
            question: "7835 + 7835 = ?",
            options: ["15670", "19536", "16512", "19872"],
            answer: "15670"
        },
        {
            question: "9726 + 3356 = ?",
            options: ["7850", "13082", "11290", "6912"],
            answer: "13082"
        },
        {
            question: "1018 + 1537 = ?",
            options: ["2555", "2664", "5170", "8184"],
            answer: "2555"
        },
        {
            question: "1723 + 6961 = ?",
            options: ["9786", "8684", "16242", "9908"],
            answer: "8684"
        },
        {
            question: "7259 + 5064 = ?",
            options: ["19596", "4746", "12323", "11570"],
            answer: "12323"
        },
    
      {
            question: "4843 + 2934 = ?",
            options: ["15544", "17322", "5406", "7777"],
            answer: "7777"
        },
        {
            question: "2487 + 8086 = ?",
            options: ["6010", "18408", "10090", "10573"],
            answer: "10573"
        },
        {
            question: "5714 + 4806 = ?",
            options: ["9372", "9436", "15168", "10520"],
            answer: "10520"
        },
        {
            question: "6820 + 9144 = ?",
            options: ["13788", "14994", "8168", "15964"],
            answer: "15964"
        },
        {
            question: "4807 + 4350 = ?",
            options: ["9157", "11502", "7680", "4702"],
            answer: "9157"
        },
        {
            question: "5337 + 8690 = ?",
            options: ["16150", "14027", "12562", "7084"],
            answer: "14027"
        },
        {
            question: "3014 + 8980 = ?",
            options: ["16982", "11994", "18158", "12464"],
            answer: "11994"
        },
        {
            question: "9106 + 7662 = ?",
            options: ["14236", "2444", "19356", "16768"],
            answer: "16768"
        },
        {
            question: "3763 + 3957 = ?",
            options: ["15754", "3450", "12470", "7720"],
            answer: "7720"
        },
        {
            question: "2706 + 6196 = ?",
            options: ["8902", "3988", "19904", "3822"],
            answer: "8902"
        },
        {
            question: "6636 + 6830 = ?",
            options: ["18900", "2858", "13466", "7936"],
            answer: "13466"
        },
        {
            question: "3974 + 7490 = ?",
            options: ["11464", "19246", "15674", "12748"],
            answer: "11464"
        },
        {
            question: "7499 + 5201 = ?",
            options: ["4972", "14556", "7354", "12700"],
            answer: "12700"
        },
        {
            question: "5639 + 8613 = ?",
            options: ["2104", "14252", "19864", "10442"],
            answer: "14252"
        },
        {
            question: "4245 + 4332 = ?",
            options: ["8948", "8577", "10802", "12350"],
            answer: "8577"
        },
        {
            question: "6485 + 9637 = ?",
            options: ["16122", "14964", "17850", "6608"],
            answer: "16122"
        },
        {
            question: "4761 + 7534 = ?",
            options: ["12295", "13284", "16352", "18304"],
            answer: "12295"
        },
        {
            question: "9853 + 6631 = ?",
            options: ["14716", "16484", "17026", "8926"],
            answer: "16484"
        },
        {
            question: "9597 + 2914 = ?",
            options: ["12511", "12630", "16310", "19010"],
            answer: "12511"
        },
        {
            question: "5849 + 6025 = ?",
            options: ["11268", "7356", "11874", "15598"],
            answer: "11874"
        },
        {
            question: "7121 + 5132 = ?",
            options: ["12253", "4958", "8068", "2972"],
            answer: "12253"
        },
        {
            question: "7529 + 3157 = ?",
            options: ["19464", "11618", "10686", "2252"],
            answer: "10686"
        },
        {
            question: "5565 + 6584 = ?",
            options: ["7888", "12902", "9712", "12149"],
            answer: "12149"
        },
        {
            question: "5153 + 8952 = ?",
            options: ["17722", "4346", "14105", "19478"],
            answer: "14105"
        },
        {
            question: "5851 + 6536 = ?",
            options: ["12186", "17936", "12387", "11600"],
            answer: "12387"
        },
];

export default level14questions;